<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on hjertnes.blog</title>
    <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on hjertnes.blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 08:07:10 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hjertnes.blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-23-cup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 08:07:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-23-cup/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made some doughnuts</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-22-baking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 07:01:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-22-baking/</guid>
      <description>We made some doughnuts last night. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More blogging?</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-21-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 06:05:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-21-blogging/</guid>
      <description>My main focus of late have been my wiki and mastodon over the last year or so.
But as 2020 are concluding I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about what I&amp;rsquo;d like to change next year. One of them is that I&amp;rsquo;ll start blogging more again.
I also made some traditional Norwegian christmas stuff for the first time yesterday:
Might also start participating the micro.blog community again. Haven&amp;rsquo;t made up my mind on that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-18-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 07:58:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-18-likes/</guid>
      <description>Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) I Just Don&amp;rsquo;t Trust Them SwiftBar Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Why does Linux have so much trouble sleeping and waking? | Hacker News Super Keybindings for Magit No recompile, no redeploy, managing features flags in .NET Core, locally and with Azure Heavy Is the Head That Wears the AirPods Max The Leica SL2-S = InstaBuy! Apple to Discontinue Music Memos App in March 10 git aliases for faster and productive git workflow How to Make Your Code Reviewer Fall in Love with You It’s Time to Embrace Kubernetes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-11-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 20:24:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-11-likes/</guid>
      <description>userland: a book about the command line for humans This Is the Coronavirus Election A Primer on the Different Types of Browser Storage | CSS-Tricks Prevent layout shifts with CSS grid stacks Shifting Winds — MacSparky Wouter: A Minimalist Alternative to React Router What’s New in Webpack 5 Understanding when to use useMemo Web Vitals Public Object: Strict vs. Forgiving APIs How Hacker News Crushed David Walsh Blog When is no-code useful?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-04-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 20:46:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-12-04-likes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;changeme&amp;rsquo; is valid base64 Redefining software quality Connecting With Friends on XMPP Roam and TheBrain, together – Coping Mechanism Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) A photo of my dog – Coping Mechanism Curbside Using Emacs 76 Bookmarks and Burly &amp;lsquo;Lives of the Stoics&amp;rsquo; by Ryan Holiday and Stephen Hanselman — Tools and Toys 73 Awesome NPM Packages for Productivity 🚀🌱 - DEV Statsviz Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Business Operations - Tech Stack Details Alex Schroeder: 2020-10-23 The finger memory of incremental search, or switching to swiper Mystery Ranch Front This Is the Perfect Keyboard C# 9 Record Factories Introducing NGINX Service Mesh - NGINX Kubernetes Ingress Controllers California appeals court rules Uber, Lyft must reclassify drivers as employees Trump&amp;rsquo;s Twitter account hacked after Dutch researcher guessed password ‎iSH Shell PSA: The “Xi&amp;rsquo;an Famous Foods” Cookbook is Available for Purchase — Tools and Toys To Eleventy and Beyond – Mozilla Hacks - the Web developer blog Gabz/mL The iPhone 12 and iPhone 12 Pro Takeaway Friday - A Stoic Philosopher in a Hanoi Prison TheBrain v12 brings Backlinks to the table Porn, Zen, and .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-20-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:49:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-20-likes/</guid>
      <description>awk Michael Fürstenberg Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Rhoneisms The Daring Fireball Election Desk Is Calling It: Biden Wins Glamour goprogressbar git-o-matic The True Name of the Bear bsag&amp;rsquo;s micro blog The Hackett File: The End of the Intel Era like a hurricane Ruby Style Guide Badges Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Election Impact Score Sheet Finally, an expensive camera I don&amp;rsquo;t want - the Zeiss ZX1 Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-13-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 21:12:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-13-likes/</guid>
      <description>Git Exercises What is Notes good for? - All this Why do we use the Linux kernel&amp;rsquo;s TCP stack? Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) duf 2020 Election Week Searches – Pornhub Insights A Visual Tour of macOS Big Sur – 512 Pixels Dear Linus…You’re wrong about the Apple M1 Twitter Rhoneisms Set in the Present Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) micro.burk.io - SourceHut Q3 2020 Financial report Alfred Ready for Apple&amp;rsquo;s M1 Chip - Alfred Blog Alfred Ready for first Apple Silicon Macs – 512 Pixels Parallels Desktop for Apple Silicon Mac Twitter Kaleidoscope In my other life… A quick hit about the big and small iPhone 12 models Two takes worth reading on the iPhone 12 Pro Max camera Am I losing interest in shooting film?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-08-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 09:08:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-08-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Changes on my wiki this week:
 Better styling for code blocks Replaed the Switch Games list with a folder and induvidual notes Replaed the Comics list with a folder and induvidual notes Replaed the Podcasts list with a folder and induvidual notes Wrote about how to keep emacs 27 from refreshing package lists on every start Wrote about a new project of mine called worklog Wrote about Dropbox, the new MacBook Pro keyboards and the touch bar  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-06-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 21:34:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-06-likes/</guid>
      <description>Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) chriswalz/bit Spotify spikes SongShift Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) The &amp;ldquo;Developer Experience&amp;rdquo; Bait-and-Switch - Infrequently Noted Defective DevOps Going Indie bsag&amp;rsquo;s micro blog The new minimum salaries in finance and tech for H1B visas Writing JavaScript tools in other languages – a new trend? Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Our Favorite AeroPress Attachments and Accessories — Tools and Toys Helge Gudmundsen Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Prediction A Short Story About SQL’s Biggest Rival Facebook, Twitter dismantle global array of disinformation networks Environment variables in Golang prisma/prisma-client-go Upgrading my music streaming setup Glow IBM to break up 109-year old company to focus on cloud growth Google’s Supreme Court faceoff with Oracle was a disaster for Google Privacy Badger Is Changing to Protect You Better Tools I use: argparse builder Bubble Tea Your Single-Page App Is Now A Polyfill Lisp and Haskell Pragmatic Bookshelf: By Developers, For Developers 39 Shirts - Leaving Mozilla Google And Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Decade-Long Copyright Battle Reaches Supreme Court Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-01-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 19:14:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-11-01-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Just pushed an update to my wiki. I have written a lot of new stuff, and updated most notes in some way. And I have also fixed the between notes links. Will probably start moving to a proper changelog next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-31-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 09:14:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-31-likes/</guid>
      <description>Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) No, C++ still isn&amp;rsquo;t cutting it. TheBrain v12 brings Backlinks to the table Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) xr: A new weapon for your regex arsenal Which Programming Languages Use the Least Electricity? – The New Stack Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Love and Monsters Reeder 5 Released for iPhone, iPad, and Mac — Tools and Toys Chemist Eggs String of Firms That Imploded Have Something in Common: Ernst &amp;amp; Young Audited Them Brian Tracy - copy-paste-shell Create TypeScript declarations from JavaScript and JSDoc - Human Who Codes Monitor Front-End Performance With Interactivity Metrics In New Relic Presenting v7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-25-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 18:55:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-25-wiki/</guid>
      <description>I brought my wiki back this week. It kind of went offline when I went from roam to org-roam. But this week I found some time to write the stuff needed to generate it.
It is generated with this script. It takes all my org-roam notes that doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain &amp;ldquo;#+private: true&amp;rdquo; and converts them to HTML with pandoc. And then this go program makes the index page.
None of it is fast, but it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-23-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 17:34:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-23-likes/</guid>
      <description>Apple Watch Series 6: Graphite Is the New Black Safari on iOS 14 and iPadOS 14 for PWA and Web Developers－firt.dev The Ugly Side of React Hooks Tmux in practice: local and nested remote tmux sessions Flashing Palely in the Margins CARROT Weather Gains Flexibility with iOS 14 Widgets, Watch Complications, and Watch Face Sharing On Modern Web Applications Stability Remembering my father Apple Watch’s Sensory Overload Go&amp;rsquo;s Major Versioning Sucks - From a Fanboy - Qvault Apple Watch Series 6 and Apple Watch SE: The MacStories Overview Apple Fitness+: A personalized fitness experience comes to life with Apple Watch Exclusive: The Billionaire Who Wanted To Die Broke…Is Now Officially Broke What&amp;rsquo;s new in C# 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing jobs</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-16-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 19:52:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-16-jobs/</guid>
      <description>I have my last day as a developer for Sbanken on Monday, and I&amp;rsquo;ll have 2ish of vacation, before I join Knowit Experience as a Senior Developer in the start of November.
I&amp;rsquo;m really excited about this for many reasons. Two of them are:
 I&amp;rsquo;ll be using a Mac at work again. After two years of Windows, I can say that everything I hated about it in 2004, is still more or less the same And I&amp;rsquo;ll be working from the city center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-16-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 19:39:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-16-likes/</guid>
      <description>bsag&amp;rsquo;s micro blog Rolling Stone&amp;rsquo;s 500 Greatest Albums 2003 v 2012 v. 2020 - Google Drive Towards principled reactive UI VSCode Tips for Power Users Commercialising quantum computers Weighing in - All this Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) [Toward a &amp;ldquo;modern&amp;rdquo; Emacs LWN.net] Fuck Clojure? No, fuck Rich Hickey. #UsToo Throw Away Code Parity Conservation SourceHut API 2.0 dev log Running numbers - All this MacOS like Fonts on Manjaro/Arch Linux Timery for Toggl Why Slow Thinkers Cannot Use GO Programming Languages?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging again?</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-10-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 19:58:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-10-blogging/</guid>
      <description>I have updated the design today. Stole some stuff from Eli and made it my own.
My wiki is down at the moment. Or not down, but there isn&amp;rsquo;t a lot there. The reason is that I had that thing, and then I migrated it to https://roamresearch.com/ and then that became https://orgroam.com/ and I have no working way to publish that in a good way. So my wiki is just for me at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-10-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 09:30:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-10-likes/</guid>
      <description>The Power of Extension Methods - Automation Mission On journaling Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Org 9.4 is out. Can you help? No TikTok For You Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) WriteFreely Deleting Adobe Twitter these days Patronage Revisited Reinstalling Emacs Packages Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Neil Young is wrong (about everything) Organizing film negatives Dickhead of the Week: Instagram CEO Adam Mosseri Helm development is now stalled · Issue #2386 · emacs-helm/helm In-App Purchase Rules – Marco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-02-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 19:59:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-10-02-likes/</guid>
      <description>The Power of Extension Methods - Automation Mission On journaling Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Org 9.4 is out. Can you help? No TikTok For You Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) WriteFreely Deleting Adobe Twitter these days Patronage Revisited Reinstalling Emacs Packages Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Neil Young is wrong (about everything) Organizing film negatives Dickhead of the Week: Instagram CEO Adam Mosseri Helm development is now stalled · Issue #2386 · emacs-helm/helm In-App Purchase Rules – Marco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-09-26-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 17:11:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-09-26-likes/</guid>
      <description>BIANCO: Pizza, Pasta and Other Food I Like it thinks I am Canadian Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Fantastical 3.2&amp;rsquo;s Calendar Widgets — MacSparky Notes on buying an Apple Watch Sport Loop :: mattisms.blog — Acros 100 in the Hasselblad Managing buckets Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Message Boards What does the future of the Apple Watch look like? Here&amp;rsquo;s the pitch. Roughly 2000 blogs running on a $7/month dyno | Hacker News Bottom Type in F# Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-09-19-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 16:11:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-09-19-likes/</guid>
      <description>Steven Levy on Steve Jobs and the G4 Cube Indian IT consultancies struggle against technological obsolescence Unofficial Guide to Datomic Internals goldmark Jeffail/gabs todocheck Design Draft: First Class Fuzzing File System Interfaces for Go — Draft Design Building strong distributed teams, one pixel at a time Go command support for embedded static assets (files) — Draft Design There will be new emojis in 2021 after all Show HN: How I made simple Geolocation service which handles 6m+ req/mo for $5 Comic for 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-09-11-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 07:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-09-11-likes/</guid>
      <description>This is what I&amp;rsquo;ll be reading today: https://www.cheribaker.com/stories/power-play/ How to Compare Objects in JavaScript Scraping Framework for Golang An intro to Go for non-Go developers Containerize Your Go Developer Environment - Part 1 - Docker Blog rodo My Ten Favorite Fountain Pens Logging in Clojure: Making Sense of the Mess Async Python is not faster Comic for 2020.06.12 How to use React Testing Library Tutorial - RWieruch Five common mistakes writing react components (with hooks) in 2020 Running Awk in parallel to process 256M records You Might Not Need UUID V4 for Generating Random Identifiers TC39, Javascript So, I went with Roam Research and am a True Believer We’ve moved – please excuse our dust Lime Text | About IHostingEnvironment vs IHostEnvironment - obsolete types in .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-09-06-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 10:09:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-09-06-likes/</guid>
      <description>Indie Sticker Pack Apple’s head of Diversity and Inclusion has left ↦ What happens when you update your DNS? Comic for 2020.06.17 Low-Background Metal Apple Threatens to Move Basecamp&amp;rsquo;s New Email App to Trash The State of Developer Ecosystem in 2020 Infographic React Hook Form VS Formik Creating a Design System in React What is React Fast Refresh? Weird Emacs: Listy Lambdas Comic for 2020.06.16 9srv.net!a: master_in_tech DRY vs DAMP in Unit Tests Use GitHub actions to publish NuGet packages Back to an iPad (ish) Millennium Problems After GitHub CEO backs Black Lives Matter, workers demand an end to ICE contract A historic “no” from Intel to Apple, then a “no” back from Apple nREPL 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-28-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 05:54:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-28-likes/</guid>
      <description>I Am Deleting the Blog Comic for 2020.06.23 watchOS 7: The MacStories Overview Comic for 2020.06.22 Modeling Study nginx ui Cyanide &amp;amp; Happiness (Explosm.net) Sharpener Review: Blackwing One-Step Long Point A little bit of plain Javascript can do a lot Exploring top-level statements in C# 9 | tabs ↹ over ␣ ␣ ␣ spaces by Jiří {x2} Činčura Real-Time Messaging In A Distributed Architecture Using ABP, SignalR &amp;amp; RabbitMQ Generating C# .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-23-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 09:40:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-23-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Not a lot of content changes this week, but I&amp;rsquo;m attempting to use Roam as my wiki. Currently I have a private and public one. All the editing and writing is done in the private one. And then I export it. remove the stuff I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be public and import it into the public one.
The process isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as I&amp;rsquo;d like, at the moment. So I will probably not update it every week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-22-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 20:17:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-22-likes/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft: Rust Is the Industry’s ‘Best Chance’ at Safe Systems Programming – The New Stack The Two Things Killing Your Ability to Focus WWDC 2020: The little stuff you might have missed Your dev environment matters less than you think Clivern/Beetle ARM Mac: Why I&amp;rsquo;m Worried About Virtualization Time to upgrade your monitor Stop caring about your code Adding host filtering to Kestrel in ASP.NET Core Introducing dotnet-monitor, an experimental tool | .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-16-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 09:15:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-16-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Updates on my wiki the last week:
 Updated the about section Copied over all my like posts up until the end of 2019. Will continue to work on that next week. The plan is to only keep 3-6 months of posts on this blog and the rest that I want to keep is on my wiki  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-14-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 07:45:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-14-likes/</guid>
      <description>Failing (and winning) at planning software projects Foam Comic for 2020.07.04 emoji-picker-element The Double-Bang (!!) Operator And A Misunderstanding Of How JavaScript Handles Truthy / Falsy Values Understanding Template Literals in JavaScript Space Basketball Hiware Extra-Wide Reusable Glass Drinking Straws twtxt file — twtxt 1.2.3 documentation Release gopls/v0.4.2 · golang/tools Defining interfaces locally Using GitHub Actions and Hugo Deploy to Deploy a Static Site to AWS Go is Boring&amp;hellip;And That’s Fantastic!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-09-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 10:39:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-09-wiki/</guid>
      <description>I have been working on some changes on my wiki this weekend:
 Some mayor changes in the structure; there will be more soon ish. Moved back to using hugo and ox-hugo to generate it. I&amp;rsquo;m really happy with the result. I think a lot of what I loved about the former format have been maintained, while not all the issues I had with the first attempt at building a wiki with ox-hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-07-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 15:14:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-08-07-likes/</guid>
      <description>Only 9% of visitors give GDPR consent to be tracked Use systemd timers instead of cronjobs Centralized logging solution Linus Torvalds on &amp;lsquo;Linux kernel in-tree Rust support&amp;rsquo; Imagining an Open Source SwiftUI scanimage: scan from the command line! Linux kernel in-tree Rust support Comic for 2020.07.11 Hamster Ball 2 Keeping Your Modules Compatible - The Go Blog Gopherize yourself How I Structure Go Packages | Benjamin Cane cosmos72/gomacro Why Go’s Error Handling is Awesome Gruber: A moment of clarity regarding the raison d’etre for the App Store Comic for 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-31-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 08:08:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-31-likes/</guid>
      <description>Don’t Close Your MacBook With a Camera Cover More than just a Twitter hack Thinking about learning Clojure OXO Good Grips 3-Piece Angled Measuring Cup Set Gabz/mL Instant Access to Your Shell Init Files Running Emacs with systemd Second day, or third ? Headless WordPress with Gatsby Cloud How to Use useDrag With React Our Transition to React Native | Khan Academy Engineering Apple Wins Irish Tax Battle Against E.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-24-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 16:11:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-24-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Changes on my wiki since the last time I wrote one of these.
 Yesterday I migrated from GitHub to Sourcehut. This have been a very long and slow process for me. On one side I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to because I think GitHub is great. On the other I felt like I had to because of their relationship to ICE. Part of the problem is also that the service I use to build and serve my websites(https://netlify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-24-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 16:11:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-24-likes/</guid>
      <description>XP.css How to prepare for losing your programming job A note on commit messages Assembly&amp;rsquo;s Perspective of C The Ten Commandments for C Programmers (1990) The Great CoffeeScript to Typescript Migration of 2017 swyx Writing | The Third Age of JavaScript immudb Up to 4GB of memory in WebAssembly · V8 How to Use Linode Object Storage The Many Faces of an Undying Programming Language — Jakob&amp;rsquo;s Personal Webpage Tin Can Magic: Simple, delicious recipes using pantry staples: Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-18-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 17:58:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-18-likes/</guid>
      <description>Sign in with Apple Zero Day All The Feelings How to code like the top Programmers at NASA — 10 critical rules - Alt Bulletin My new blogging workflow Amazon.com: Cryptonomicon (9780060512804): Stephenson, Neal: Books A few things I learned this month Why does OpenBSD still include Perl in its base installation? go-interview Optional JSON fields in Go - Eli Bendersky&amp;rsquo;s website Book Review: Writing an Interpreter in Go Instrumentation in Go What is a goroutine?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to my wiki</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-11-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 10:17:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-11-migration/</guid>
      <description>My wiki have been my main website for a while now. I&amp;rsquo;m in the process of migrating the content of this blog over to it. I just removed all the &amp;ldquo;status&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;micro blog&amp;rdquo; posts. The next steps would be to go over everything and re-write it as something on my wiki for everything in the archive. It won&amp;rsquo;t be a simple move but a longer process and probably many re-organizations in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-11-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 09:34:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-11-likes/</guid>
      <description>Gabz/mL Comic for 2020.06.03 Eventual Consistency German city wants to ditch Microsoft for Linux Why don’t we listen style9 Hooked on Redux React Hooks — Now what do I do? 4 Ways to Conditionally Render in React Stupid Things - Vol 1 .NET async/await in a single picture – TooSlowException Getting started with React Test-Driven Development 101 with jest 201: Core Web Vitals, aspect-ratio, and RWD turning 10! | CSS-Tricks The Joy of Serverless The Hard Part of Learning a Language • Hillel Wayne GitHub Etiquette Habits of High-Functioning Teams Why is Kubernetes getting so popular?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-05-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 11:56:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-05-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Updates to my wiki.
 Update about text Added link to my twtxt Added snotgirls to comics Wrote about what is coming in Emacs 27 Fixed various mess ups in the formatting Added a list of podcasts I listen to  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-03-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 20:45:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-07-03-likes/</guid>
      <description>Advice to New Managers: Don&amp;rsquo;t Joke About Firing People Following the protests on social media GoodLinks Review: A Flexible Read-it-Later Link Manager Packed with Automation Options ★ On Apple Announcing the ARM Mac Transition at WWDC This Month Pastel Review: A Modern Color Utility for iPad and iPhone IBM no longer developing facial recognition ↦ “The Champ” Detrola Watch by Shinola Show HN: Top, but for Nginx Comic for 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-06-26-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 19:11:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-06-26-likes/</guid>
      <description>Racket is 25 years old stup Tmux for mere mortals Comic for 2020.05.10 Jack White’s Lazaretto Ultra LP Has A Dozen Hot New Gimmicks! Forget tabs – the new war is commas versus spaces: Web heads urged by browser devs to embrace modern CSS My second brain. The Ideal iPhone App First-Run Experience Is None At All Azure Service Bus Queue vs RabbitMQ - Which Programming Languages Use the Least Electricity?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-06-14-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 12:42:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-06-14-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Not done a lot on my lately
 Added a section about Music, and a thing about Nirvana Added a section about Firefox  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-06-13-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 08:17:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-06-13-likes/</guid>
      <description>Facebook Acquires GIF-Sharing and Creation Platform GIPHY for $400M Comic for 2020.05.16 ‘Weird’ by Olga Khazan Comic for 2020.05.15 mozilla-spidermonkey/jsparagus Eero in the Apple Store Is It Laziness Pre-order “The 99% Invisible City” Coffee Table Book by Roman Mars and Kurt Kohlstedt Common Cold It&amp;rsquo;s A Good Day My React components render twice and drive me crazy How to CSS Style in React - RWieruch Dan Abramov on Twitter: &amp;ldquo;This hits the nail on the head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-06-05-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 05:41:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-06-05-likes/</guid>
      <description>Representing JSON structures in Go - Eli Bendersky&amp;rsquo;s website [Mocking time and testing event loops in Go Dmitry Frank] Comic for 2020.05.22 Support Single-File Apps in .NET 5 (https://xkcd.com/2309/) John Wiegley on Emacs 27 | Irreal Apple Releases iOS 13.5 with COVID-19 Exposure Notifications, Face ID Bypass for Masks, FaceTime Setting, and Apple Music Stories Sharing Is Shopify ready to be double-crossed by Facebook? Conditional rendering in React Native may crash your app 15 React Best Practices You Need to Follow in 2020 Become a better godfather for your React components Announcing React Native for macOS and more · React Native for Windows + macOS Pad thai med tofu og reker - Oppskrift - Godt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki update</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-31-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 13:46:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-31-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Just updated my wiki.
 Added a section for my GitHub sponsors Added a section for food and wrote about my sausage toppings Added a section for when I take notes while watching a movie or TV show.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-29-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 09:44:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-29-likes/</guid>
      <description>Programming Idioms BGP Why I stopped using Microservices - RWieruch How to use React Ref - RWieruch Bye, Amazon You might not need switch in JavaScript The Devastating Decline of a Brilliant Young Coder 6-Foot Zone Sourdough Starter Use or Discard By Coronavirus Genome 2 Turtle Sandwich Standard Model 2020 Google Trends Zeal - Offline Documentation Browser Drafts is Now a Wiki mbmbam Today’s Javascript, from an outsider’s perspective | Lea Verou Prototyping at Slack I wrote Task Manager and I just remembered something&amp;hellip; Rainer Joswig on Twitter: &amp;ldquo;#lisp history tidbit: The original .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-24-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 15:41:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-24-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Some recent changes to my wiki. Haven&amp;rsquo;t done it in a while, because I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time.
 New articles  X-Pro 2 Minimalism Pens I no longer use Inks I have used Bad paper Paper   New section about Tmux2 WIP  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-22-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 19:45:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-22-likes/</guid>
      <description>Keys.pub – Manage cryptographic keys and user identities [PHP showing its maturity in release 7.4 LWN.net] gRPC vs. REST: Performance Simplified is-promise post mortem Things I Wished More Developers Knew About Databases Rules of Thumb for a 1x Developer A visual guide to React Mental models The New New Working From Home Set-Up Away from keyboard Spotify is really the new radio The inevitable has happened. The case against CS master’s degrees The Open Web Is Dying Documenting Go Github Repo Learn Svelte - Scrimba Playlist BBEdit gets revamped Markdown preview ↦ Iconfactory&amp;rsquo;s Tot updated for&amp;hellip; less color ↦ SSH hacks – a little sanity for remote workers What the right to repair movement gets wrong How to Get to Know a New Programming Language The final Python 2 release marks the end of an era - Stack Overflow Blog What does the &amp;lsquo;rc&amp;rsquo; in `.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-16-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 09:14:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-16-likes/</guid>
      <description>10 Practical JavaScript Tricks Windows Terminal Preview v0.11 Release | Windows Command Line DevDocs What&amp;rsquo;s coming in Go 1.15 Bagels Oatmeal New Grad vs. Senior Dev Rob Pike interview for Evrone: “Go has become the language of cloud infrastructure” When does React re-render? Explaining rerenders and how to optimize performance Mozilla: *Privacy Not Included Michael Fürstenberg Michael Fürstenberg Is it Yoga, What I need? Unbroken. Like seagulls. On Microcasting 🙌🏼 📌 Separate Yourself From Your Ideas by Greg Morris Stop Giving af!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-08-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 19:12:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-08-likes/</guid>
      <description>Redis 6.0.0 GA is out! -  Comic for 2020.03.28 Comic for 2020.03.31 Comic for 2020.04.01 Comic for 2020.04.19 Comic for 2020.04.20 Comic for 2020.04.21 Comic for 2020.04.22 Comic for 2020.04.24 Comic for 2020.04.25 Comic for 2020.04.26 Comic for 2020.04.27 Comic for 2020.04.28 Comic for 2020.04.29 Comic for 2020.05.01 Comic for 2020.05.02 Comic for 2020.05.03 Comic for 2020.05.04 Comic for 2020.05.05 Books I recommend to my software engineering students - Austin Z.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-03-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 18:05:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-03-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Not a lot of changes to the wiki this week:
 Moved two items from articles to programming Two new articles on ordering with intention and digital hoarding  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Likes</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-01-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 08:35:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-05-01-likes/</guid>
      <description>Reading: Trust Me I’m Lying Comparing HTTP/3 vs. HTTP/2 Performance Stop using client-side route redirects Retool – build internal tools fast. Coronavirus Charts All Fish, all day ★ COBOL, Programming, and Coding John Conway, RIP GitHub is now free for teams Getting started with TiddlyWiki: a beginner’s tutorial - Ness Labs Comic for 2020.04.14 John Conway Dies From Coronavirus Like it or not, COBOL keeps on running ↦ An experimental JavaScript toolchain | Rome RIP John Conway Technical reasons to choose FreeBSD over GNU/Linux Twitter Gets Squeezed John Horton Conway (1937-2020) Why I’m leaving Elm - lukeplant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-04-26-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 20:55:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-04-26-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Just posted some updates to by wiki.
Here is a summary:
 Added an arcitle about a golang trick that took me forever to figure out Added some notes on coffee gear Added a pice on env variables Played around with literate programming in org-mode Added a &amp;ldquo;journal&amp;rdquo; about my iOS homescreen Added a OSX trick when emacs can&amp;rsquo;t read some folders Updated about me Added two emacs acticles: helm and ivy and why I don&amp;rsquo;t use deft Fixed a link styling issue  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-04-20-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 16:37:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-04-20-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Updates to my wiki.
 Removed the WIP comment on using Removed the &amp;ldquo;Disable OS X icons&amp;rdquo; link Removed the &amp;ldquo;Emacs:&amp;rdquo; on all the emacs package articles Added three new emacs packages: multi-cursor, aggressive-indent, git-gutter Rewrote &amp;ldquo;pile of instapaper hacks&amp;rdquo; to a updated article on link sharing Added section on Text editor fonts Added section on Text editor themes Added section on Window management on OS X Added a tricks seciton with two of my favourites &amp;ldquo;defaults write&amp;rdquo; hacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-04-11-wiki-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 19:18:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-04-11-wiki-updates/</guid>
      <description> Replaced uses with using Added section called &amp;ldquo;code&amp;rdquo; where I&amp;rsquo;ll link to code repos. Wrote a short thing with some thoughts about Svelte Added some more notes about starting a company Wrote a thing about my experience using different editors for Golang Added a journal for changes to my emacs config.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-03-29-wiki-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 08:31:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-03-29-wiki-updates/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the styling a little Added a section called Thinking loud and a section about me thinking about starting a indie company. Wrote about VPN&amp;rsquo;s  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-03-22-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 10:23:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-03-22-wiki/</guid>
      <description> Moved a lot of the stuff from the Personal section to a new Articles section. Moved links to https://home.hjertnes.blog/ Updated the workout routine log I wrote about my experience using Mastodon  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-03-08-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 14:51:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-03-08-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Not a lot of new stuff this week, but I have worked on some stuff this week.
 The org file my wiki was generated from is now included, will soon add a link to it and the github project A links section. The idea is to add links I use all the time to this one A Journal section. The idea is to add some limited in scope or time &amp;ldquo;blog like&amp;rdquo; series of texts here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates in the last two weeks</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-02-23-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 09:07:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-02-23-update/</guid>
      <description>Most of my focus at the moment are going into my wiki, but because I don&amp;rsquo;t have or want a RSS feed there, I&amp;rsquo;ll write every week or every two weeks here about the changes I have done there.
 I took all my blog post drafts I had and added them to the wiki Did some simple re-organisation. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably do more of it next week. Went through everything and updated it And I&amp;rsquo;m also playing around with the non stable version of Emacs again, the upcoming version 27.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking a break from Micro.blog</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-02-21-bye/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 18:56:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-02-21-bye/</guid>
      <description>Recent happenings here at Micro.blog have gotten me to taking a break from Micro.blog. It might be a short term or I might never come back. I have added all the RSS feeds of the people I followed to my RSS reader, and if you want to talk I&amp;rsquo;m always available on https://keybase.io/hjertnes. I&amp;rsquo;m not removing my site from Micro.blog for now, but I might do that in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki updates</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-02-09-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 20:04:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-02-09-wiki/</guid>
      <description>I have moved my wiki off from hugo to being one large HTML document instead. My friend @eli first did it, and I decided to do the same myself. The reason is that I write my wiki as a large org file, and this kind of output reflects what I see it as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes after listening to ATP 364</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-02-07-fucking-atp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 13:44:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-02-07-fucking-atp/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t listen to any tech podcasts anymore, because they bore me to death. The closest is probably Go time, a podcast about the Go Programming Language. But @eli talked about how dumb the hosts were being so I decided to listen and post my reactions to it.
 Oh my fucking god. So much talk about all kinds of bullshit&amp;hellip; SwiftUI Who the fuck writes a view that is hundred or hundreds of lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent stuff on my wiki</title>
      <link>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-01-26-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 06:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hjertnes.blog/posts/2020-01-26-wiki/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll try to do this each week. But it will probably more like most weeks. Just a recep of what I have been doing on my wiki. Last week I worked a lot of the template to make it show everything more likea a outline inside of a large cloud of entries and tags. And I also updated most of the pages in it. Plus that I re-organized everything into a intial structure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
